Guide to the Thomas Cover Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Publications, Series 2
  - Capacity theorems for the relay channel (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Relativistic information flow and the twin paradox (Stanford Engineer), fall/winter 1979 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Multiple access channels with arbitrarily correlated …, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Multiple access channels with arbitrarily correlated … Stat #41, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Competitive optimality of logarithmic investment, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Competitive optimality of logarithmic investment Stat #34, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Problems appearing in gentle diversions, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Multiple user information theory Abbas El Gamal and Tom Cover (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Asymmetries in relativistic Inf. Flow Stat # 38, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Multiple user information theory for the Gaussian Channel, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - An achievable rate region for the multiple-access channel …, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - A rate region for the multiple-access channel with feedback (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Maximum entropy and conditional probability Stat #32 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Asynchronous multiple access channel capacity Stat #35 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Historical comments on nearest neighbor pattern …, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - [label missing] (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Merging for optimal symbol detectors" by Juan B. Riera, 1976 Aug (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Achievable rates for multiple descriptions, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Achievable rate for multiple description Stat # 43 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - An information theoretic proof of Hadamard's inequality, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - An information theoretic proof of Burg's maximum entropy, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - An information theoretic proof of Burg's max. entropy … Stat # 49 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - An algorithm for maximizing expected log investment by T. Cover (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - On the similarity of the entropy power inequality and the … Stat # 48 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kolmogorov complexity, data compression and inference, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Kolmogorov complexity, data compression and inference (NATO, France), 1983 Jul (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Monotonicity of linear separability under translation, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Monotonicity of linear separability under translation (T. Cover and A. Bruckstein) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Review of "Probability and information" by Yaglom, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - JASA book review on Probability and information, by Yaglom and Yaglom, English ed., T. Cover (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Empirical Bayes stock market portfolios, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Empirical Bayes stock market portfolios Stat # 54 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Introduction, Chap.1, Open problems in computation …, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Simplex conjecture, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Finite memory clocks, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Communication complexity of shifts, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Ergodic process selection, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Pick the largest number, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Gambler's ruin: a random walk on the simplex, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The entropy power inequality and the Brunn- …, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Figure-ground problem for sound, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Conjecture: feedback doesn't help much, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The capacity of the relay channel, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - [unlabeled], 1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - A proof of Burg's theorem, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - A proof of Burg's theorem (T. Cover and B.S. Choi), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Conditional limit theorems under Markov Conditioning, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Conditional limit theorems under Markov Conditioning Stat # 58 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - A conditional limit … Cover and Choi (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - A sandwich proof of the Shannon-McMillan-Breiman Theorem, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - A sandwich proof of the Shannon-McMillan-Breiman Theorem P. Algoet and T. Cover, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - A sandwich proof of the Shannon-McM-Breiman Theorem, P. Aalgoet & T. Cover Stat # 55, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - A bound on the financial value of information, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - [unlabeled], 1988 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Asymptomatic optimality and Asymp. Equip. Prop. of Log-opt Stat # 57, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Drafts, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Game theoretic optimal portfolios, by R. Bell and T. Cover: Stat # 60, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Game theoretic optimal portfolios, by R. Bell and T. Cover, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - The role of feedback communication, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - The role of feedback in communication T. Cover (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Determinant inequalities via information theory (by T. Cover) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Determinant inequalities via info. Theory by J. Thomas and T. Cover (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Gaussian feedback capacity by. T. Cover and S. Pombra (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Gaussian feedback capacity Tech. Report No. 63 Cover & Pombra (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Drafts (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Feedback increases capacity of Gaussian channels by at most half a bit … by S. Pombra and T. Cover (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Kolmogorov's contributions to information theory and alg. Compl. Stat # 69 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Maximum entropy and the lottery Stat # 62 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Do longer games favor the stronger player? By T. Cover (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - On the competitive optimality of Huffman Codes, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - On the competitive optimality of Huffman coding (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Log (1/p(x)) codes are shorter more often than not by T. Cover (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - The entropy of Markov trajectories, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Universal portfolios, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Universal portfolios Stat #66 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Successive refinement of information (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Successive refinement of information Stat #71 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The entropy of a randomly stopped sequence, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Minimum complexity density estimation Stat #68 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Information theoretic inequalities, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Information Theoretic Inequalities (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Information theory and the stock market, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Reprint of 1990 Shannon Lecture in IEEE IT Society newsletter, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Shannon lecture (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Invited response to G. Gilder's article (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Handbook of coding theory (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Which processes satisfy the second law?, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Brazil IT talk (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Review of "complexity,entropy & the physics of information", 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Non-white Caucasian multiple access channels, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Non-white Caucasian multiple access channels drafts (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - On the maximum entropy of the sum of two dependent random variables, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Collier's Encyclopedia "Info - Th", 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - On the exponential value of labeled and unlabeled samples, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Relative value of labeled and unlabeled samples in pattern recognition …, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Universal portfolios with side information, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Universal data compression and portfolio selection, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Data compression chapter in Handbook of Electrical Engineering, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Electrical Engineering Handbook (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Comments on broadcast channels, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The cost of achieving the best portfolio in hindsight, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - The efficiency of investment info., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Universal portfolios with short sales and margin, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Shannon and investment, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Shannon reminiscences, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Growth optimal investment in horse race markets with costs, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Performance of universal portfolios in the stock market, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - The worst additive noise under a covariance complaint, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Unified duality between channel capacity and rate distortion with state info., 2001 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Claude E. Shannon, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Duality between channel capacity and rate distortion …, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Different views of the 2nd law of thermodynamics, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Minimax regret portfolios for restricted stock sequences, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - A statistic for measuring the influence of side info in investment, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence Info. Th - 1 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence Info. Th - 2 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Elements of information theory - reviews (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Complexity of Classification Algorithms in Pattern Recognition (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - More Results on 1:1 v/s U.D. Codes, 1975 May 16 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Talks, Series 3
  - Descriptive complexity on topological spaces, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ISLA talk: competitively optimal investment, 1979 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A critical look at sufficiency, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Italy, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ISL, 1979 Oct (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - I. T. Brighton, 1965 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 3rd IT symposium - Tallinn, USSR. Ashkelon, Irsael, 1973 June (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fourth annual communications theory workshop, 1974 Apr. 22-24 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Communicdations theory conference - Minneapolis, Miss, 1974 June (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ISIT Conference, Notre Dame, 1974 Oct.27-31 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - UCLA Colloquium, Los Angeles, 1976 Feb.27 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Las Vegas talk, 1980 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - URSI Conference Boulder CO Network Information Flow, 1982 Feb.12-14 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Goodman ISL - summary in EE 370: Information Theory, 1981 Sept. 30 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AIDS conference LV Gambling systems, 1980 Nov.5 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Santa Cruz talk, 1980 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - MIT Talk: Information theory of multiple systems, 1980 March 31-Apr.4 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - NTC talk: mult. User, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NATO talk England, 1980 Aug (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Santa Monica - I.T. Sym., 1981 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Hungary talk, 1981 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ORSA taalk, 1982 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Optimal investment algor. Les Arcs, France, 1982 June (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Les Arcs, France, 1982 June (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Las Vegas/Info Com transparencies, 1982 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Repeated play against … Les Arcs, France, 1982 June (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - URSI meeting, Boulder, Colo., 1982 Jan.13-15 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - EE undergrads: gambling and the stock market, 1983 Dec.5 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - JSEP review, 1983 Nov.17 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - EE orientation by Macovski, 1983 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ORSA-TIMS Conference, Chicago, 1983 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Maximum entropy workshop, Wyoming, 1983 Aug.1-3 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Int'l Symposium on Information Theory, Quebec, 1983 Sept.25-29 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Maximum entropy workshop, Laramie, Wyoming, 1983 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Kiefer/Wolfowitz, 1983 July (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Condit limit theorems: Canada IEEE IT, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Kiefer/Wolf Cornell mtg., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - ASA lunch meeting, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - GSB finance talk, 1983 Nov.15 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Info theory, Brunn, Minkowski, CLT, etc. IEEE Canada IT, 1983 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - CDC Conference, Las Vegas, 1984 Dec.12-14 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - O.R.dept. talk, 1984 Oct.17 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Tashkent, USSR talk, 1984 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 6th Int'l Symp on Information Theory, Tashkent, USSR, 1984 Sept.18-22 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Gopi meeting: computation and communication Morristown NJ, 1984 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - ISL Affil mtg, 1984 Feb.17 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Stock market investment theories (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Info theory & stock market EE 200 seminar, 1984 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - EE 370 research survey (by B. Gray), 1984 Sept. 22 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - CDC Conference, Las Vegas, 1984 Dec.12-14 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Symposium on I.T. Tashkent, USSR, 1984 Sept. 20 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - EE 370 Fac. Summary talk, 1985 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Empirical Bayes portfolios Brookhaven Nat. Lab. New York Conference, 1985 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - IT talk: Cover, Csiszar, Choi, 1985 June (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Affiliates talk, 1985 Feb.22 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Arrow-Wilson seminar - interdisciplinary seminar in decision analysis Economics 386, 1985 Feb 19 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - UC Berkeley talk, 1985 Feb.12 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Specific problems in communication and computation (SPOC*85) Morristown NJ, 1985 Aug.14-16 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 5th workshop on maximum entropy and Bayesian methods in applied stat. Laramie, Wy, 1985 Aug.5-8 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - ASI on Performance Limits in Comm. Theory & Practice, Tuscany Italy, 1986 June 7-19 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - IEEE Information theory workshop, 1987 June 21-15 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - NATO Advanced study institute (ASI) Italy, 1986 summer (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Jacob Marschak Inter'd Colloquium UCLA, 1986 May 23 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - SPOC, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Adaptive stat. procedures and related topics Brookhaven Nat. Lab, 1985 June 8-11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Washington DC, 1985 Apr.2-3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - TIMS/ORSA Boston, 1985 Apr.29-May 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 15th ann. Communication theory workshop Sanibel Isl., Florida, 1985 Apr. 21-24 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Swedish-USSR Int'l workshop on information theory, Granna, Sweden, 1985 Apr.14-19 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Research briefing on computer vision … Nat. Rsch Council, Washington, 1985 Apr.2-3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Suran Analysts Workshop, Washington DC, 1985 Mar. 24-25 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Int. symp. On information theory, Brighton UK, 1985 June 23-28 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ISIT, 1985 June (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - MIT workshop on distrib. Algs. "Role of feedback …", 1986 Oct.22-24 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Feedback increases capacity … Cover and Pombra, 1986 Mar. 6 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - NATO - ASI, 1986 July 7-19 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sunday contribution to Ziemba short course, 1986 Apr.13 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - UCSD research trends in comm. Theory, 1986 April (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Info theory and investment: ISL Affil. Meeting, 1986 Feb.20 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ORSA-TIMS, 1986 Apr.14 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - UCLA Marschak lecture talk, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - UCSD conference - Center for magnetic recording res., 1986 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 16th annual communications theory workshop, Palm Springs, 1986 Apr. 27-30 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - ORSA-TIMS meeting, Los Angeles, 1986 Apr.14-16 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 25th IEEE Conference on Decision and Control - Athens, Greece, 1986 Dec.10-12 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - MIT Distrib. Algs. In communication and computation, 1986 Oct.21-23 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Int'l symp. On Information theory Ann Arbor, MI, 1986 Oct.5-9 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 10th annual conf. on information theory - Prague, Czech., 1986 summer (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Information theory workshop - Bellagio, Italy, 1987 June 21-25 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - IEEE communication theory workshop - Florida, 1987 Apr. 26-29 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - JPL Faculty Days program, Pasadena, 1987 Apr. 23-24 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - University of British Columbia talk, 1987 Jan. 20 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Schilling NSA short course, 1986-87 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Third Int'l workshop on information theory (Joint USSR-Swedish) - Sochi, USSR, 1987 May 24-30 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - IT workshop, Italy, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - T.C./Kolmogorov talk, 1987 Nov.25 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Stanf. Stat. Universal portfolios, 1987 March (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Univ. Brit. Columbia talk, 1987 Jan. 20 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - CIS research abstracts, 1987 June (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Information theory and … (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Sochi, Russia talk, 1987 May 22-30 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Neural networks for computing - Snowbird, Utah, 1988 Ap., 6-10 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Some dualities between information theory and investment: talk, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - A bound on the monetary value of information: talk, 1984 Aug.6 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Stock, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Information inequalities, 1988 June (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - A bound on the financial …, 1988 June (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Neural net lecture, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Int'l symposium on information theory - Kobe City, Japan, 1988 June 19 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Competitive optimality, 1988 June (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - I. T. Thursday talk: information theory and investment, 1988 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Universal portfolios (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - SRI talk, 1988 Feb (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - ISL Affil., 1988 Feb (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Information theory and the stock market UC Davis '90 and ER370, 1990 Oct.17 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Information theory and the stock market, 1989 Nov.14 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Information theory and the stock market, 1989 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - "Information theory and the stock market" IMS meeting, 1989 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Information theory and the stock market - Bell Labs, 1989 July (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Chicago trip, 1989 Nov (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - IMS conference, Washington DC, 1989 Aug.6-9 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AT&T Bell Lags Gen. Res. Coll. New Jersey, 1989 July 21 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - IEEE/CAM Info. Theory Workshop, Cornell NY, 1989 June 25-29 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "Information theory and the stock market" AT&T Bell Labs, 1989 July (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Performance weighted portfolios, 1989 July (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Successive refinement of info., 1989 June (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - JSEP, 1990 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - T. Cover research review, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ASA meeting - Anaheim, 1990 Aug 6-9 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Communication theory workshop, 1990 June (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Learning with finite memory (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Non-white Gaussian channels with feedback, by Sandeep Pombra, 1991 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Refined descriptions: Ojai Comm. Theory, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - On some relationships between info. Theory, economics, and statistics, 1990 Aug (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Information theory and investment, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - ASA meeting, San Francisco: Optimal stock market portfolios, 1990 Feb 21 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - A factor of 2 (Sh. Lecture), 1990 Jan (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Statistics days at FSU - Florida State University, 1990 March 23-24 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - A.S.A. talk on sports statistics, 1972 and 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Do longer games favor the stronger player?, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - TIMS ORSA - Caesars, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1990 May 7-9 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - ASA meeting Optimal Stock Market Portfolios, 1990 Feb.21 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - IEEE Int'l Symp. On Info. Theory, San Diego, 1990 Jan.14-19 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "What processes satisfy the second law?" Spain, 1991 Oct (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - EE 370 faculty research review ISL seminar, 1991 Sept (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - COLT, 1991 Aug (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Determinant inequalities via information theory (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Limits of multiple acces comm. SLAC, 1991 May (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - EE 200 ISL faculty research ISL presentation, 1991 Oct (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - A merge interpretation of the Theil entropy, 1991 June (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Limits of multiple access …" Wireless symposium, 1991 March (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - The acceleration of wireless … - Stanford, 1991 May 22-23 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Neural networks for computing - Snowbird, Utah, 1991 Apr.2-5 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Foundations of randomness - Stanford CA, 1991 March 4-7 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - ASA meeting - Anaheim, CA, 1990 Aug.7 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - NIPS conference, Denver: Complexity & General. In neural nets, 1992 Dec.1 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - EE in year 2000 - EE faculty retreat, 1992 Nov.14 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Information theory and stock market - Texas A&M University, 1992 Oct.6 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Info. Theory and the stock market - Xerox Park, Palo Alto, 1992 Sept.24 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - "What processes satisfy the second law?" Salvador, Brazil, 1992 June 22 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - DARPA Workshop - Chapel Hill, 1992 June 10-11 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Stanford NFC workshop - Results in pat. Rec. & Neu. Nets, 1992 June 5 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - HP talk: Duality of data compression and gambling, 1992 Apr.2 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Sports statistics - Pomona College, 1992 Apr.22 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Univ. of Wisconsin distinguished lecturer series: I.T. and the stock market, 1992 Apr.27 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Univ. of Wisconsin Info. Theory and the Stock market, 1992 Apr.27 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Admitted applicant's day Stanford, 1992 Apr.2 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - DARPA Workshop - Salt Lake City, Utah, 1992 Jan.6-7 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - JSEP talk, Stanford, CA, 1993 Aug.23 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - ARPA meeting, Pittsburgh PA, 1993 July (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Stanford Telecom Center Symp. CDMA, FDMA, & TDMA, 1993 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - JAREC Forum, Hakone, Japan "Natural role of relative entropy …", 1993 Mar.14-19 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Int'l Symposium on Information Theory, San Antonio, TX, 1993 Jan.18-22 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - DARPA Workshop, JPL, Pasadena, CA, 1993 Jan.14-15 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - ITW '93: IEEE Info. Theory Workshop, Japan, 1993 June 4-8 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Princeton Universal Prediction, 1994 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Data Compression Conference - Snowbird, UT, 1994 March 29-31 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Info Theory & the Stock Market" - Pomona College, 1994 Feb. 9-10 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "Rate Distortion for Images" - Stanford ARPA, 1994 Jan (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - EE201 Faculty Research Review (ISL) - Stanford, 1994 Oct 10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ISL Faculty Research, 1994 Sept (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Wireless Communication" - Alexandria, VA ARPA Meeting, 1994 July 26 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "Universal Portfolios with Memory" - ISIT '94 Trondheim, Norway, 1994 June 23-July 4 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Information Theory & the Stock Mkt" - Wells Fargo, San Fran., 1994 June 3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Comments on the Geometry of Information" - S. Fe, 1994 May 15 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Minimax Regret Portfolios - Math Finance, Cambridge, 1995 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Mathematical Finance - England, 1995 March 12-25 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Minimax Regret Portfolios" - INFORMS, Atlanta, Georgia, 1995 June 15 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Info Theory and Investment - Math Finance, Cambridge, 1995 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "Theoretical Limits on Communication" - Stanford Telecom, 1995 March 6 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "Information and Statistics" - Alexandria, Virginia, 1994 Oct 7 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - "Information and Statistics" - IEEE Workshop on Information Theory - Alexandria, VA, 1995 Oct 27 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Role of Feedback in Gaussian Channel" - CCCSP (Kailath) Stanford, 1995 June 22 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Multiple Access Investment" - IEEE Workshop, Poland, 1995 June (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Information Limits on Communication - Santa Cruz, 1995 April 23-26 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Image Compression - Telecom Workshop, 1995 Sept 13 (Box 4, Folder 21)